Those who ceaselessly hone the art
of killing are known as masters.
These lethal abilities, dutifully
passed down through many generations,
have become what are
called modified bloodlines.
This is the story of one such master,
Hikaru Gero of the Poison Clan
and his greatest challenge yet,
to get married.
No mama, lots of time
Run,
Thank you for
being so patient!
Got those towers for ya!
I hope Gero's up for this.
So this is a college welcome party.
I've heard the legends.
I never thought my job would take me here.
New students! Move in!
Let's hear it for all of us starting
college and meeting for the first time!
Cheers!
You're a first year, right?
Is the party getting
you excited for school?
Huh?
Hey?
Uh-huh. Yeah.
I'm having tons of fun over here.
What did we say?
We're just gonna go.
Yeah, see you around.
This is my chance to talk to
upperclassmen and I blew it!
I want to hire you as a bodyguard for my
niece who starts university this spring.
If possible, be discreet.
I don't stand out.
I'm Shiori Ureshino.
Her father was my older brother.
He built this company from the
ground up in a single generation.
He passed away from an illness a year ago.
But according to the terms of his will,
Shiori will succeed him as
CEO once she comes of age.
However, there are some who didn't
agree with his final decision.
My older sister, for one.
She claims Balzac is rightfully hers.
No question about it.
Cards on the table, I don't
know what she'll attempt?
But rumor is, she's gone and
hired a professional herself!
Someone with strange techniques
that no ordinary expert can stop.
I'm grateful, I need help,
so thanks for taking the job!
Your student ID, don't lose it.
Starting today, you're
Daigo Oshima, a third year.
You're kidding me!
Sorry, ma 'am, this is sudden.
But could we maybe,
if it's possible, go to a drinking party?
Sorry, but that's a risk
we don't need to take.
Please, can I go?
Okay, only this once, though.
Okay, who's up next?
I'm Shiori Ureshino, a
first-year economics major…
and I like…
I did it again?
What should I say?
I am pleased to meet you.
Huh.
Well, thanks a lot for that introduction.
Okay, next person.
Can you handle a party, Gato?
I've had drinks with the
Bugmaster loads of times.
You've got me worried.
I'd better sneak in.
You'll see.
I'm not just a master assassin.
I'm also the life of the party.
Name's Oshima. Econ major.
Now observe as I chug eight pints at once.
What is this, a 90s movie?
Now for the grand finale.
We should call an ambulance, shouldn't we?
Here comes the applause.
Great to meet you all.
It's a water-absorbent palmer!
It's completely harmless!
That's nasty!
Anybody else who hasn't
introduced themselves?
Hey, man, you're up.
Hmm.
My name's Naruko.
That's all.
How about your first name? Your major?
You know, stuff like that.
That's unimportant.
Huh?
The only thing that truly matters
is that I was fortunate enough.
to meet all of you here in this moment.
For that, I thank my lucky stars.
What's his deal?
He's been spaced out this whole time.
Super thank them.
That had no substance.
And why did he say it twice?
I searched for you.
My true love.
Naruko, is the seat taken?
How come I can't make a first
impression as good as this weirdo?
It's gotta be his books.
These drinking parties, it
appears they have hidden depths.
Is this all?
Listen, Ureshino.
I'm sorry!
Don't lash out at her
because you're trick-bombed.
I swear, if you make her cry...
What? Come on!
I didn't say anything!
I just don't understand why you're
forcing yourself to go to these.
I get you're inheriting a company and
trying to overcome your social anxiety,
but there's no need to force yourself.
Huh?
What did I say?
Really, ghetto?
No, I'm not sad.
Just overwhelmed you
care about how I feel.
The truth is, it's not about the company.
What I want is to be able to
fit in with everyone else.
When my dad reached the
end, he said to me...
You should give drinking a try, but
be sure to wait until you're twenty.
My Shiori you're a nice
girl i mean that but
you worry too much about
what other people think.
Trust me you've got to
take everything that's
pent up inside and bam let it all out like
a Firework enjoy life
and the time you have
with others above all
else i want that for you.
I can't do it.
Even here with you.
I still freeze up.
And the words refuse to come up.
It takes time.
I know it.
You don't have to say it.
The hardest part is taking the first step.
After that everyone will accept me.
But I can't help worrying.
What if they get sick of me
the moment I open my mouth?
What if I annoy them or make them angry?
There was still time and I didn't even
have the courage to talk to my dad.
Never know why he named
me as his successor.
And not someone else.
That's why I want to improve myself.
To face the things that scare me so one
day I could laugh away fear you know.
Someone's out to kill you right oh but if
you want to go somewhere I won't stop you.
My job is keeping you safe and
nothing will get in my way.
Madame, I have your report.
Her bodyguard is good.
Well, he might act laid back.
He leaves no openings.
I super forgot to charge my phone.
Is this a game to you
I've given you an entire
month and you've made
zero progress what am I?
paying you for a party supply company with
a market cap of 1.5
trillion yen is at stake
As if that meek little
girl is fit to take over
so tell me how long
until you dispose of her?
Hmm, in a while, when it's right!
Excuse me, don't give me
this when I'm ready crap!
I'm paying you to!
This bodyguard, Oshima!
You say he's good, but
he's still a nobody!
And wouldn't last a second
against a master like you!
Madam, I'm a man of my word.
In any case,
either convince that brat to renounce her
inheritance or leave her
unfit to inherit anything.
If killing her is what it
takes, then by all means.
Gato,
you realize you're not a real student
and don't have to listen to the lectures.
I've never been in a classroom before.
This is fun.
That backstory is hella tragic.
One more day.
You there, in the hoodie.
Name a product that
transformed its industry?
Mixy mix, max mix.
A hundred of these kits were made
for the brand's 30th anniversary.
It's Candy's holy grail.
Not bad.
Looks like at least one
of you knows their stuff?
It renewed the Mixi-Mix market!
A return to the Mix-a-sance!
Because of Mixi-Mix Max-Mix! Fact!
As long as there are
passionate students like you,
I could retire and leave things
in the next generation's hands.
I should have known.
Since they can't separate me from the
target, they're using brute force.
Who here looks suspicious?
They're outside.
I already made sure no one had
line of sight into this room.
That attack affected
the whole lecture hall.
However, this is a well-ventilated
environment, ruling out a gas attack.
Which would mean...
He injected himself with something
that allowed him to move.
Sound waves transmitted remotely,
to shake the room and its occupants.
His equilibrium should
have been scrambled,
but somehow he's
super-recovered in no time flat.
No one could pull off such a precise,
large-scale attack, except...
There's only one person who could
produce a cure like that in an instant.
A poison master.
Ghetto!
The client's been informed.
Making it look like an
accident saves trouble.
That's Hitman 101.
Ureshino.
Clearly, their intention
was to eliminate you.
What's the plan?
Do we skip the camping trip tomorrow?
That's up to our client.
Of course you can go.
Really? I can?
Absolutely.
You've been looking forward
to this trip for ages, right?
There's no substitute for the
fringe you'll make at university.
Meet as many as you can.
Besides, with those two around,
there's nothing to worry about.
Good morning.
Uncle Mitsuki, I'm leaving.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
No worries.
That's kind of a huge bag, though.
What did you pack?
A collapsible umbrella.
Have a safe trip.
Actually, the rest is secret.
Even if she stayed home, there's
no way to guarantee her safety.
The only way to end this
is confronting the enemy.
And unlike with Himekawa, we don't
know when the Soundmaster will strike.
Is the plan to settle things on this trip?
Hey, what does this mean?
An important promise I can't bring.
You're so thoughtful, Maruko.
I've got a promise I want to make you.
How about you make one with me
first, since I'm closer than her?
There, we can't!
It's super important.
A man who can cook is three
times hotter to the ladies.
Time to unleash those
skills on the public.
I'll show you I can compete
with the best of them.
Yakisoba, I made it myself.
Want to try some?
Anyone?
It's delicious.
Yakisoba.
Should we step in?
Have fun and don't worry about me.
That's what Ureshino told us, remember?
This is something she wants
to figure out herself.
Alone.
What can I do?
To get them to the lake.
Sigh, water, stir away, chopped ginger,
rice, pepper, and all-absorbent pollen.
Plenty clubs, wild
chihuahuas, fortune tellers.
Is she okay?
If talking to people doesn't
work, I'll try a new approach.
I like the magical girl get-up.
As you can see, the cloche is empty.
Now for the magic words.
Pon poodoo pin poodoo pom po poon.
Pin poodoo pom poodoo pom po poon.
And for my next trick,
an extra big helping.
Pin poodoo pon poodoo pom po poon.
You okay?
Those were some pretty nifty magic tricks.
My family's business
sells lots of magic stuff.
I've never performed in front
of a group of people before.
Plus I messed up the finale.
As you know I'm not too good with words.
Suddenly it all flooded
back the performance Mr Gato
put on at the party and I
thought to myself that's it.
So thank you.
I didn't really um humble but weird I mean
what was that glad I could inspire you.
I didn't think to ask until
this moment but have any
of you guys heard about
the curse of Lord Cladney?
What's that?
At one point this used
to be a village they
had a local deity and
they made offerings to it.
Up until world war ii every couple
years the crops would fail so the
villagers would pick out the youngest
child and sacrifice them to this god.
They would lock them up inside of that.
shrine over there.
After the war, they abandoned the custom.
But landslides, fires, and several
other disasters followed at its peak.
Nearly a thousand people lived here.
These days, it's nothing but a ghost town.
Even now,
Lord Cladney waits for his next
offering and that sacrifice.
That's not true.
Even if it isn't, not like
anyone enjoys a spoil sport.
Oshima.
All of it was true, every last word.
Well, I would say that
was plenty of build-up.
Yep.
Now, let's get this party started.
It's the moment you've all been
waiting for, the test of courage.
Hey, have you seen Naruko?
I'd love to pair up with him.
The melody of this
forest is super perfect.
Shiori Ureshino, my killer
session with your screams.
Begins now.
Is. I.
I. Do.
I. I.
I.
It smells like a headache,!.
It smells like you are
just a moment?. Now!.
It smells like a headache,!.
It smells like you are just a moment?.
Bye bye?.
Such?.
I don't want to go to a
person like a problem?.
I'm like a problem?.
I'm satisfied that I'm comfortable?.
I'm like my pain?.
I got you die?.
Just, just, daisuki shakena, baby?.
Yodon-dai hoshiki ni susumetani?.
Tokimeki daisuki shakena, baby?.
Namai-ki na tai-do-de-dai-gassho?.
Escape is super impossible?.
What the heck is that?
Hang on tight!
I've never been in a better condition
You've gotta seize this opportunity!
Super water-absorbent polymers?
Next time, Lord Cladney.